https://www.otisfcu.coop/privacy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footer MenuJoin CloseBecome a Member CloseRatesNews CloseWhat’s NewCommunity EventsPress ReleasesOTIS Quarterly NewsletterFor Sale CloseResources CloseImportantDisclosuresFeesLinksMFA Information and FAQsPenaltiesPopularReport a Lost or Stolen CardSurcharge-Free ATMsSenior$afe ResourcesWiring InstructionsDirect Deposit Instructions CloseContactCareer
FACTSWHAT DOES OTIS FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?WHY?Financial companies choose how they share your information. Federal law gives members the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.WHAT?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the products or services that you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and payment historyCredit history and credit scoreHOW?All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons OTIS Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes OTIS FCU share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes–such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYESNOFor our marketing purposes–to offer products and services to youYESNOFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYESYESFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–information about your transactions and experiencesNOWe don’t shareFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes–information about your creditworthinessNOWe don’t shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNOWe don’t shareWho is providing this notice?OTIS Federal Credit UnionHow does OTIS Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to persons who need to know that personal information to provide products or services to you.How does OTIS Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youOpen an account or deposit moneyPay your bills or apply for a loanUse your credit card or debit cardWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.Why can’t I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlySharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes–information about your creditworthinessAffiliates from using your information to market to youSharing for nonaffiliates to market to youDefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.NonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Joint marketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Questions?Call (207) 897-0900 or go to www.otisfcu.coopPrimary Sidebar Apply for a LoanApply online securely. Apply for a Credit CardTwo great options! Loan CalculatorMember News & UpdatesMore Member News & UpdatesFooter Physical Address:
170 Main Street, Jay ME 04239 Mailing Address: PO Box 27, Jay ME 04239 Phone: (207) 897-0900 or (800) 848-3688
Fax:  (207) 897-3927 Routing Number 211287609Connect with OTIS FCU!
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Yelp
LinkedIn
Hours & Contact InformationATM LocatorReport Lost or Stolen CardBecome a MemberWiring InstructionsDirect Deposit InstructionsApply for a LoanVehicle – Cars, Trucks, SUVsRecreational Vehicle LoansFixed Rate Home Equity LoansMobile Home Loans
Privacy Policy | Website Privacy Policy | Truth In Savings | Disclosures | Accessibility Statement
Out of concern for the health and well-being of our employees, our members, and the wider community, we have made the decision to temporarily suspend all in-branch banking, effective November 24th, 2020.CLICK FOR IMPORTANT DETAILS
